I'm not waiting around for some damn kid.
He's late.
Your watch is fast.
You say if there's one thing I am, it's never late.
I say I'm gonna be somewhere, I'll be there like a flash.
Nice car, man. What is this, real leather?
I got places to be, small fry.
What do you got for me?
I got some great stuff here, Mr. Hannison.
I'm talking top of the line.
You've been busy.
You know, you know, idle hands, empty pockets.
So what do you think?
I think you're 200 for the lot.
It's worth like 10 times that much.
And I told you I don't handle this nickel-dime crap anymore.
You land a real score, you come talk to me.
Until then, you take what I give you.
Maybe. I should just take it all.
That isn't a threat, is it, kid?
The Woman About Top Gear
I'm looking at the
Wings.
.
You don't have to worry your mother with any more of this stuff.
That's all.
Dad, we both worry about you.
What Jarrell did to you because of me.
Wait a minute. I knew what the risks were, Clark.
And I'd take them again in a heartbeat
if it meant keeping you safe.
The two and I have a game to catch.
Metropolis Sharks, 50-yard line.
Lex really came through this time.
Look, son, I understand what that friendship means to you,
but please don't forget he had you investigated.
Be careful.
I'm not going into this with my eyes closed.
He wants another chance to prove he's changed.
Clark.
Dad, this is my senior year.
I don't want to have to worry about Lex or Jarrell or any of that.
I just want to live a normal life,
hang out with my friends and play football.
All right, why don't you go get the truck.
We don't want to miss the kickoff.
You can tell my dad he'll pay for everything.
It's...
Store.
But I don't want to miss the kickoff.
Not on the roof.
Take this.
That is for show.
Talk to the delivery jaw.
That's the worst I've ever had.
When did you start a career here?
As favourite actor.
It's an impression of Split enabling children.
See when they grow up?
Yeah.
you had to push me out of the way.
Dad, it wasn't me.
I saw someone who can move like I can.
I couldn't believe it.
He saved you.
Whoever it is, not only did he save my life, Clark,
he also stole my wallet.
Somebody save me.
Let your wounds break right through.
Don't care how you do it.
Just save me.
Stay.
Come on.
I've been waiting for you.
I made this whole world shine for you.
Stay.
Come on.
Hey.
Aren't you two supposed to be at the game?
Well, the tickets to the game were in my wallet,
which was stolen.
Some kid swiped it outside the medical building.
Oh, my god.
You were robbed?
Are you all right?
a very fast pair of sneakers.
But I'm going to call the credit card company,
report it stolen.
Hey, Dad, wait.
This kid, he was as fast as I am.
I should find out who he is.
Just let me talk to Chloe.
Maybe she can track down where he's been using your card.
Come on, Dad.
If I don't find anything by the end of the day,
then make the call.
All right, but I want you to be careful, Clark.
We don't know anything about this kid.
That's why I have to find out who he is.
Are you sure you're OK?
Sweetheart, I'm fine.
I wish you wouldn't worry about me all the time.
You were in a coma for three months, Jonathan.
It's hard not to worry when you've been through so much.
A little help from modern medicine,
I plan on going through a whole lot more,
starting with a romantic evening with my beautiful wife.
Thought maybe we could have a little dinner
and then drive on down to the lake.
I'd love that, sweetheart.
But I might have to work late again tonight.
Running the Talon is a lot more involved
than I thought it would be.
But, uh.
I'll call you later, OK?
Head over to the library.
I need a beer.
All right.
It's gone now, you dirty.
I'm going to pay for that.
I left my wallet there.
Watch your mouth.
You're an idiot,
punk.
Um, thanks a lot.
I appreciate it.
Thanks.
Love you, Laurel.
And you, sir.
You too, Simon.
before I came back from Paris.
Really?
Well, why didn't you tell me?
I could have come with you and gotten a mermaid or an anchor
or a mermaid holding an anchor.
What?
I didn't plan on getting it, all right?
It kind of just happened.
Tattoos don't just kind of happen.
There's usually some ink and a fair amount of paint involved.
Well, what was I supposed to do?
Ask you for permission to get it?
Whoa, hey.
That's not what I meant.
Why are you biting my head off right now?
I'm not.
Yes, you are.
Look, I just...
I don't want you making a big deal out of this.
I don't care about the tattoo, okay?
But what bothers me is the fact that, for some weird reason,
you felt like you had to hide it from me.
I've seen what keeping secrets has done to my parents.
I'm not going to end up like that.
Jason, the last thing I ever want to do
is hurt you.
But there are some things that I am just...
I'm not comfortable sharing with you yet.
I'm sorry.
I'm losing it.
I'm gonna get my dad's wallet,
then you and I are gonna sit down for a long talk.
Not big on the chitchat, dude.
Smiley later.
Dad, I found the key to Stoia Wallet,
but I lost it down at the docks.
He just took off across the water.
Uh, son.
Son.
Hey, Clark.
What took you so long?
Dude, I didn't think anybody else could move like that except me,
because, hey, best man alive, right?
Yeah.
You were right on my butt, man, and, you know, I've always wondered
if there was anyone else out there like me,
and it turns out to be you, Jimmy Crack Corn, fresh from the farm.
What kind of story did you spin to con my dad
off a free meal and a bed on the couch?
No story, Clark, just the truth.
And what's that?
All right, well, a couple years ago, there was, like, this accident, right?
And there was this huge flashlight,
and then my body went into overdrive.
And this happened in Smallville?
No.
And this is my first time here, and no offense, dude,
but hopefully the last.
I've never met anyone with powers like yours
that wasn't from around here.
Yeah, well, maybe she'd get out more.
I don't know.
So, how'd you get so fast?
You been acting too, or...?
Just kind of born this way.
Why are you living on the streets, Bart?
What happened to your parents?
Your son got zapped into a human lightning bolt.
That's what happened.
I mean, they made this whole big deal
that everything was gonna be okay, and that...
I don't know, man.
You should have just seen the way they looked at me, huh?
I could tell that nothing was gonna be the same.
So you ran away?
I...
I just didn't fit in.
Man, I guess you don't want that problem.
Oh, you'd be surprised.
I ran away once, too.
Yeah, why'd you come back, man?
Mow the lawn? Milk the cows?
Dude, you should be out there with me, tearing it up.
You mean stealing everything in sight?
It's not like I ever really hurt anybody.
I mean, I usually just swipe a little bling
from the stiff upper crust whenever I need some cash.
I want you to call a have-not, Clark.
I take from the haves.
Like my dad?
Look, man.
Don't even sweat it, okay?
They don't charge you if your card's stolen.
Oh, and that makes it all right.
Look, man.
My fence down in the suicide slums, they sure changed me.
So I had to boost your dad's card in order to get a room.
I don't like spending the night out on the streets.
Okay? Stuff happens there.
Okay.
When I'm asleep, I'm just as slow as everybody else.
Don't hit me with the big cow eyes there, Stretch.
Okay? I could always take care of myself.
Yeah, you've done a great job so far.
You know what, man?
Enough about the poor little street urchin, right?
Let's take a closer look at the mysterious Clark Kent.
Let's see.
You like to read about Native American mythology?
Yeah.
You've scrolled the name Lana on all your notebooks.
And you have one of the most boring hobbies known to man.
Rock collecting.
I don't collect rock.
Dude, are you okay?
Get that away.
I'm allergic.
Man, I've heard of people sneezing around cats and dogs,
and stuff, and never getting all weak, and the knee is over a rock.
It's a long story.
Which is one I'm sure I would love to hear.
After we get back.
Get back from where?
Anywhere we want.
I mean, dude, we are two super-powered studs here.
Why else do you think I came to Smellyville looking for you, man?
Let's go crank it up. Go have some fun.
You ever seen Florida?
Yes.
Dude, man, that girl on the black bikini, she was totally checking you out.
No, she wasn't.
Look, the girl was eyeing you like you were a snow cone, dude.
You should've gotten her number.
I can't just walk up to a girl on the beach and get her phone number.
Yeah, well, lucky for you, I can.
You should have to call her next time you're in Miami.
What? Shh.
I can't just go run back down to Miami.
Why not?
Because it's, it's what?
Too much fun, Clark?
Come on, dude, nobody's ever died from it.
What are you doing?
I'm eating a cookie, dude. I'm starving.
You can't just take whatever you want.
Mom runs this place.
Look, man, there's a line.
I don't do lines.
What's up, Kent?
I thought you'd still be in Metropolis playing detective.
I thought I'd leave that one up to the authorities.
Never would've caught him anyway.
Chloe, this is my friend Bart.
He's from the future.
Really?
Yeah.
I ran all the way back in time to tell you that we're still in love 100 years from now.
Bart, what's your favorite kind of flower, Chloe?
Uh, tulips.
How did you do that?
Magic.
Oh.
You wanna see some more?
Clark.
Knock it off.
Your dad called.
Is that the boy who robbed him?
Yeah.
His name's Bart Allen.
Why is he here?
I think he's lonely.
Wants to be my friend.
Good.
Maybe you can talk some sense into him.
Oh, I'm trying.
Oh, um, Lex is looking for you, sweetheart.
He asked if you'd stop by the mansion.
He said it's important.
Okay, but I probably shouldn't leave Bart alone.
I really don't think he'll notice you're gone.
I'm sorry.
I purchased this from a private collector in St. Petersburg.
Convincing him to part with it required quite a few glasses of vodka and a small fortune,
but it was worth it.
That's very nice.
Take a closer look at the border design, embedded glyphs, similar to the Kuw Palm symbols
found in the cave.
No one spent more time down there.
than you.
Any idea what they mean?
No.
But I thought you weren't interested in this stuff anymore.
Oh, I'm still interested, Clark,
just not obsessed.
Which is why I'm not keeping this from you.
I'd like it
if we could work on this mystery together.
I'd like that.
So what is it?
It's the last surviving page
from a 14th century manuscript.
It depicts the Grand Prince Donskoy's victory
over his mortal enemy, Momai,
at the Battle of Kulikova.
Legend has it
that this was the only object
adorning the walls of Rasputin's chamber
while he studied at the Vercatoria Monastery.
He believed this page
would reveal a path to unimaginable power.
Rasputin would stare at it
for days at a time.
Tempting him penetrated secrets.
That's incredible.
Don't.
I've had state-of-the-art security
installed to protect it.
I'm keeping it at the mansion
for a few days before it goes into the vault
at Luthor Corp.
I'm sorry, Clark, I have an appointment.
Why don't you swing by tomorrow
and we'll roll up our sleeves.
Yeah.
Dude, you know Lex Luthor?
What are you doing here?
Well, Chloe shut me down,
but, you know, her loss.
Man, this place is awesome.
I mean, have you seen all the cool stuff?
You were just in there?
Yeah, I just took a quick spin.
Don't worry, man.
She won't even have a clue.
You gotta get out of here.
Clark.
Who are you talking to?
Dad.
Hey, Clark.
Just in time, son.
Your mom's working late again,
so I thought maybe we'd have guys night.
You know, catch up on the...
highlights of the game we missed?
I saw something in Lex's dad.
It was a page from an old manuscript
and it had Kryptonian symbols on it.
Kryptonian symbols?
Were you able to read them?
It had a message.
Repeated over and over.
Looked deeper.
I used my x-ray vision
and I saw a map hidden underneath.
A map?
Map to what?
I don't know, Dad,
but I think it has something to do with Jarrell
and what he sent me
after when he was controlling me.
I want you to leave this alone.
No, Dad.
Son.
You're just telling me how you want to have
a normal senior year, right?
Well, how does traipsing across the globe
on Jarrell's crusade fit in with that?
It doesn't.
But hanging out with Bart reminded me
that I'm not normal, Dad.
Maybe it's time I stopped running from who I really am.
What you really are is a 17-year-old boy.
Um, sit down.
Dad, it doesn't matter how old I am.
Whatever Jarrell sent me to find,
I have a feeling he's very powerful
and dangerous.
Especially if it falls into the wrong hands,
and I'm the only one who can stop that from happening.
How?
By stealing this manuscript from Lex?
No, he has no idea what he has.
All I have to do is sneak back in there
and get a better look at it.
Clark, it's a bad idea.
He could see you.
I'll be in and out before he even knows I'm there.
Dude!
Lex's place was sweet.
I mean, that guy's got, like, 20 cars, man.
There's no way you get that rich planet straight.
Man, I gotta step it up a notch,
because that is definitely how I want to live.
Listen, Bart, there's something I gotta take care of, all right?
Well, can I come?
No.
I mean, it's personal.
But maybe we'll hang out when I get back.
Well, dude, there's this midnight showing
of Speed at the Man's Chinese Theater.
Best popcorn and Keanu rules in that one.
So do you want to go?
You know, it sounds great, but, uh,
just don't mention it to my dad, okay?
Okay.
Clark.
I'm sorry.
Man, it's been really cool hanging out
with somebody like me, you know?
So I got you something,
just to say thanks for everything.
It's an mp3 player.
That way you can download all your favorite tunes
and listen to them wherever we go.
Where'd you get this?
I got it for you, Clark.
It doesn't matter where I got it.
Yes, it does, Bart.
You haven't been listening to anything I've said to you.
You can't go around stealing whatever you want.
Why not?
Because there are laws.
For normal people.
And, dude, why do you treat your abilities
like they're a curse?
They're not, man.
They're a gift.
I'm gonna use them.
I'm not saying you shouldn't.
Just use them to help people, not hurt them.
Who am I hurting?
The store that I swiped this from?
Because they're insured.
That doesn't make it worth it.
That doesn't make it right.
Whatever, dude.
I'm not sticking around for another lecture.
What are you gonna do, run away again?
You're not gonna solve all your problems like that, Bart.
Look, I'm not running away, Clark.
I'm running towards something.
I'm gonna have everything that I've ever dreamed of,
one way or another.
Bart.
Look, I thought you and I were the same,
but I was wrong.
You are nothing like me.
.
Oh, how rigged.
He
don't know to believe my tr comunque
dage
re. .
Bart.
Don't move!
Bart?
What the hell are you doing here?
Would you like to explain what happened here?
I just came by to say hello.
Next thing I know, all these alarms and lights were going off.
It's a little late for a, uh, social call, Clark.
Yeah, I just... I should have called, but I just figured you'd be up.
Are you sure you didn't see anyone else when you came in?
No, I didn't see anyone.
Then you don't know who did this.
No, I don't.
I believe you.
I know a real friend would never lie to me.
I better go and let you take care of this.
I'll let you in on a secret.
I'm not that worried.
You said this manuscript page was worth a fortune.
It is.
And there aren't that many fences in Metropolis that can move such a high-end item.
If I put the word out, I'm sure some fiscally challenged citizen will point me in the right direction.
You really think that'll work?
Don't worry, Clark.
Our thief is gonna learn that there's a man in the house.
And that there's nowhere on Earth he can run from Lex Luthor.
I'd like that too, Jonathan, but I can't.
Because I still have all this work to do.
I'll be home as soon as I can. That's the best I can do.
Okay, bye.
You're working late?
Oh, God.
It's like this never stops.
I don't know how.
Well, you managed all this and went to school too long.
It wasn't easy.
But I don't remember staying this late after closing every night.
Well, it's easier to do this here than at home.
Is everything all right, Mrs. Kent?
Oh, Jonathan thinks the only reason I took this job is to help out with our finances.
Oh.
I love him.
So much.
But after everything that's happened, all his health problems,
the only time I'm not worrying about losing him is when I'm here, working.
But if you're here all the time, then I'm...
You don't see him anyway.
Isn't that like you've lost him already?
A summer in Paris has really given you some insight, Mom.
I might've lost him just to remind me a little.
I don't think I do after father'simo.
A prova?
Alone, all on the same TV?
Hi.
I have a hope you'll find a new job.
What does that mean?
A huge цipck now, to find new one on.
It's going on about you.
So I'm going to be part of theuras and each one of us gets something we can work with.
This doesn't get any better apart from an answer like that.
Oh, thank you for reminding me.
Reminding you of what?
It's about time.
Well, I had some things to take care of.
Maybe when you grow up, you'll understand how men do business.
It's grown up enough for you?
It's a start.
Mr. Luther, I believe I have something that belongs to you.
Is this the dangerous criminal you warned me about?
Hey, it's not your problem.
Well, let's go.
Let's talk about that finder's feet.
He's just a kid.
Let him go.
No.
You have no idea what that freak is capable of.
If I were you, I'd be more concerned about the police right now, Anderson.
What did you do?
In about five minutes, this place will be swarming with Metropolis PD.
Well, okay.
I guess we better hurry this up, huh?
Tony!
Let's go.
Look at the mess you made, kid!
Let's see if you're faster than a speeding bullet.
You don't want to be here.
You still think what you do never hurts anyone?
Lex.
Lex?
I am sorry, Clark.
I'm sorry.
This doesn't change anything.
No.
You don't understand.
It'll kill me.
You're not a murderer.
That's not who you are.
You don't know who I am.
Yes, I do.
Bart, I saw you save my dad.
I've seen the good in you.
Art, you've got to stop running.
Or in the end, you'll just be alone.
And you don't want that.
I know you don't.
I know because down deep, we're the same.
I wish that was true, Clark.
I should have
you when I saw that.
They're all dangerous.
You have no idea where Bart could be?
Lex was unconscious.
I stayed with him until I heard the police sirens,
then I went after Bart.
By then, he could have been halfway around the world.
I think it could be for the best, Clark.
Dad.
Now, look, I know how much you wanted to help him out,
but you can't force people to change,
no matter how strong you are.
He's not a bad kid, Dad. He's just different.
At least he's willing to accept that.
Clark, embracing your abilities and flaunting them
are two entirely different things.
I know.
It's just sometimes there's a part of me
that wishes I could be more like him.
I mean, I spend so much time trying to hide who I really am,
I'm starting to feel like two separate people.
Clark, I think you'd be really surprised
to find out how many normal people feel exactly the same way.
Hey, it's not everybody who has secrets.
Yours are just...
They're just bigger than most.
I better go check on Lex.
All right, you want to use the truck?
No, I, um...
I kind of want to stretch my legs.
Hey.
Thought you'd be at work all day.
Well, that's one of the benefits of being the boss.
I've been working all day.
I promoted Linda to assistant manager
so I could take a break and spend some time
with a ruggedly handsome farmer.
Well, you're in luck.
There just happens to be one
sweating in your driveway right now.
Maybe I should get the hose and a bucket of soap.
I've really missed you.
Me too.
This is amazing.
When Clark first found these caves,
I had no idea why he was so obsessed with them.
I always felt like he was keeping these secrets from me
because he was afraid of how I was going to react.
I don't want to live like that.
I don't want to be afraid all the time.
You don't have to be.
Not with me.
That's what I've been trying to tell you.
Okay.
Do you remember the church we went to in Paris?
Yeah, when I had to leave early
to make arrangements for your birthday.
All right, well, after you left,
I noticed something strange on the tomb of Countess Thoreau.
There were these symbols etched into the rock,
like the ones in this cave.
How's that possible?
I don't know.
And when I touched them,
there was this blinding light and then pain.
And all I remember is waking up the next morning
to you knocking at my door.
And I had this.
Okay, wait a second.
So you're saying
that some strange symbols on the tomb of a dead countess
gave you a tattoo?
You know how it sounds.
Why do you think I didn't want to tell you?
That's why you left Paris.
I had to come back to these caves.
I had to find out why I was missing 12 hours of my life.
But all I found were more questions.
And I found that, of course,
I didn't know what to do with it.
I had to find a way to get it back.
I found it.
What does this symbol mean?
I don't know.
Jason, I don't know what's happening to me.
Okay, hey.
Whatever it is,
we'll figure it out together, okay?
Okay.
Clark.
It's good to see you keeping normal hours.
Just came by to see if you were all right.
I heard you ran into some trouble in Metropolis.
News travels fast.
Curse of a small town.
So what happened?
I decided to play cowboy and got my spurs handed to me.
To be honest, I don't know why I'm not dead.
There must be someone watching over you.
In more ways than one.
How'd you get this back?
I didn't.
It was sitting on my desk when I returned from the hospital.
Whoever took it must have had a change of heart.
I guess he did.
I'm glad you're feeling better.
Look, we'll have plenty of time to study this later.
Right now I'm still nursing a bit of a headache.
I'm just glad you're feeling better.
Clark.
I thought you'd like to know I had the manuscript page examined.
By a team of experts.
As soon as it turned out.
Do you know what they discovered?
That I paid too much for it.
Thanks for checking in on me.
I'm sorry.
I'm leaving.
I knew the prince would return.
I made the caught.
He kept it safe for me and The Master of Alchemy.
I've made the time to believe whatever partners I set up.
You know I had a problem.
It's the last plan.
Hey.
It makes no sense.
I don't get this stuff.
What's this doing here?
I'm sure the Queen was acting apeal.
Ms. Ish, listen.
I think you know what you're doing.
Did do the crime.
I wish.
I spent a whole night down in suicide slums
trying to convince someone that I had a thousand of these defense.
A few guys pointed me in the direction of Hanneson.
Look at you, channeling your inner criminal.
So, um, what are you gonna do now?
I don't know. I'm gonna hit some big world.
Figure out how to check it out.
See if there's anyone else out there like us.
Maybe start, like, a club or a league or something.
You know, you could come with me.
Or you could stay.
You have a great life, Clark, but...
it's not mine.
I have no reason to stay in Smallville.
You have me.
Thanks for being my friend.
Are you sure there's nothing I can do to change your mind?
Tell you what.
If...
you can catch me...
I'll think about it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Come on, I got this.
I got this!
Look at you, it's...
You have to remember this from the heart
that I used to have way back when.
I just feel this way, not anymore.
Slightstruck by the small swats,
felt very big for my little Dysol.
I tried my best to stay in my high-wnock erudite mood,
I just had three首,
and execution became my hero.
I was always just a loonyощo.
I was never let down,
I was never struggling,
I always didn't beg to do anything.
But I can tell you,
Feels like, feels like you're changing
I don't know, I don't know